

ABDALLAH KASHTA

Web Developer / Multimedia artist

About Me

Bringing over five years of diverse freelance experience in multimedia arts, content creation, and web development. Transitioning to a dedicated role in web development to drive innovation in digital spaces, echoing my adaptability and commitment displayed across various trades and roles





abdallahkashta0@gmail.com

469 Manuel L. Quezon, Taguig - Metro Manila

Language

- Arabic
- English (intermediate)
- Tagalog (basic)

Expertise

- Creativity
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Interpersonal skills
- Team work
- Problem Solving

Experience

Multimedia artist

Taguig - Philippines / Cairo - Egypt 2019 - 2024

Over 5 years of freelance experience in multimedia arts, my skills and potential give me a significant advantage in modern-day trends and technology. my skills includes, graphic design, video editing, photoshop.

Content Creation

Taguig - Philippines / Cairo - Egypt 2021 - 2024

Proficient in content creation leveraging expertise from diverse locations. Demonstrated success in harnessing the power of content creation for unlocking present and future opportunities in my field.

Web Development

2023 - 2024

During my studies in IT, I gained practical experience developing multiple websites utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP. Eager to expand my skills further and achieve success as a web developer.

Customer service representative 2022 - 2023

Obtined an excellence in interpersonal skills and service delivery in my 1 year exprinece as a CSR

Education

National University - Manila Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2020 - 2024

My excellence in academic activites lead to success and climbing into dean's list multiple times

Skills Summary

Multimedia Arts	67%
Content Creation	85%
Graphic Design	78%
Web Development	55%
Video Editing	85%





CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION

This certificate is awarded to

Abdallah Kashta

For being an active participant in

#GENERATION HIRED

CONNECTING EDUCATION TO EMPLOYMENT

this November 23, 2023 in partnership with National University

Given this 5th of December, 2023

Erica Pascual

Marketing & Growth Supervisor



CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST CERTIFICATE

Presented to

Abdalla Mohyeldin

Given on May 2023 for successfully completing the Customer Service Test provided by Mangtas.

THANK YOU FOR YOUR STELLAR PERFORMANCE!





REFERENCE NO: 3161101





CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

THIS CERTIFIES THAT

Abdalla M. Ahmed Mohyeldin

has completed the training program for New Real Estate Salespersons on

REAL ESTATE BROKERAGE: RESA/IRR		credit units
CODE OF ETHICS		credit units
TAXATION (TRAIN LAW RA 8424)		credit units
REAL PROPERTY TAXATION		credit units
DOCUMENTATION AND TITLING PROCESS	2.0	credit units

Credit hours: 12 units Course completed on: July 16, 2023 Program Accreditation No.:

Date of conduct: July 14-16, 2023 Control No.: BL TMDC CX2T U5E5 7RRQ 2023-029-1439

TRAINING VENUE: ONLINE PLATFORM

REAL ESTATE CENTRE BLDG. 10 NARRA ST. GEV, PASIG CITY



MARIA TERESITA CANLAS

PRESIDENT







awards this

Certificate of Recognition

to

Kashta, Abdallah Mohammed

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology with Specialization in Multimedia Arts & Animation Dean's Second Honor List, 3.38 GWA 1st Term, AY 2021-2022

Given this 6th day of December 2021 at National University, Manila.

Arlene O. Trillanes

Dean, College of Computing and Information Technologies

Marc Rey D. Salido

Director, Student Development & Activities Office



awards this

Certificate of Recognition

to

KASHTA, ABDALLAH MOHAMMED

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology with Specialization in Multimedia Arts and Animation Dean's Second Honor List, 3.30 GWA 1st Term, AY 2020-2021

Given this 11th day of January 2021 at National University, Manila.

Arlene O. Trillanes

Dean, College of Computing and Information Technologies

Marc Rev D. Galido
Director, Student Affairs Office